{
    "id": "7648ace2e57e4b288c312452c902460a",
    "title": "Subject – verb agreement worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "137964c4dfeb4998aa87270ba4f074de",
            "title": "Subject-Verb Agreement Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "There ………………… many objections to the plan.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "is",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither his father nor his mother ……………….. alive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Iron as well as gold ………………… found in India.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "No news ……………….. good news.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The great poet and novelist ………………. dead.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "is",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which one of these umbrellas ……………… yours?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "is",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Every leaf and every flower …………….. stripped off the tree.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Milton is one of the greatest poets who ………………. ever lived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dacoit and his followers ……………… escaped.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "None of you ………………. done the work correctly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}